LINDSAY HARTMANN

ABOUT ME

Hello! My Name is Lindsay Hartmann. Over the past 12+ years I've held different types of leadership roles with my primary focus in Human Resources and people development.

I live in the St. Louis area with my husband, our two cats, and two dogs.

A couple things that describe my personality best are that I'm an analytical thinker and I enjoy engaging with people. This is what has helped me to be successful in Human Resources.

CONTACT

Phone: (618) 201-0827

Email: lindsay@lindsayhartmann.net

EXPERIENCE

Sr .Lead-BPHR

INFOSYS - ST. LOUIS, MO

2019 - PRESENT

Owner of HR operations over five states, covering 1500+ employees. Subject Matter Expert of performance management representing 3200+ employees, HRIS, Attrition Analytics and retention plan creation and execution. Contributed to several creation and adaptation measures of new US HR policies in addition to employee and leadership engagement.

Sr. Human Resources Assistant

AMAZON - EDWARDSVILLE, IL

2017 - 2019

Manager of multiple projects and situations in a dynamic environment with proven ability to take calculated risks. Subject Matter Expert of site HR investigations and Roster.

Human Resources Executive Team Lead

TARGET - ST. LOUIS, MO

2016 - 2017

Developed and implemented a strong training culture while proactively planning for hiring needs. Highly influential store level role where I was able to utilize my skills to inspire exceptional associate performance.

Operations Manager

VERA BRADLEY OUTLET - CHESTERFIELD, MO

2013 - 2016

Mentor for store leadership teams across the country. Established operational best practices and policies. Main point of contact for payroll and benefits administration for store team.

Loss Prevention Manager

MACY'S - ST. LOUIS, MO

2012 - 2013

Developed staff of loss prevention detectives to investigate both internal and external cases of theft and fraud. Analytical manager utilizing video technology, Key Performance Indicators, and exception based reporting to initiate internal investigations involving theft, fraud, and workplace violence.

Loss Prevention Supervisor

KOHL'S - ALTON, IL

2006 - 2012

Recruited and trained all new LP Officers across multiple store sites. Created store awareness programs addressing theft, safety, inventory, and operational controls. Lead a team of loss prevention officers. Conducted internal and external investigations.

EDUCATION

Southern Illinois University Edwardsville

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE - GEOGRAPHY

Graduated 2012

Spatial research based discipline with a focus in Geospatial Information Systems and Meteorology & Climatology.